<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>AMRhub</title>
    <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on AMRhub</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ru-RU</language>
    <copyright>IACMAC</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AMRmap</title>
      <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-map/</guid>
      <description>AMRmap (AntiMicrobial Resistance Map) is a web platform for analysis of AMR data in Russia that contains a set of tools to visualize the data on distribution of antimicrobial susceptibilities and main genetic resistance determinants in clinical microbial isolates. The AMRmap database accumulates the data from prospective multicenter AMR surveillance studies conducted by the Institute of Antimicrobial Chemotherapy (IAC) and the Interregional Association for Clinical Microbiology and Antimicrobial Chemotherapy (IACMAC).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMRpaint</title>
      <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-paint/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Feb 2019 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-paint/</guid>
      <description>Paint Antimicrobial Resistance Data is the application that transforming figures to unusual abstract pictures. These pictures are filled with fancy patterns, come in a range of colours, and remind us -Science always relies on creativity! The application based on real MIC (minimum inhibitory concentration) distributions. After the choice of appropriate parameters: Organism Group, Species and Antibiotic, a user will run a special algorithm converting initial indicators to a final image. The attribute is a special colour assignment for each microorganism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMRseq</title>
      <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-seq/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-seq/</guid>
      <description>AMRseq is a powerfull web-tool for analyzing bacterial genomes and predicting the presence of resistance genes for antimicrobial drugs. A key feature of this resource is an updated database of resistance and protein genes, as well as a specially developed algorithm for double search and control.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMRbook</title>
      <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-book/</guid>
      <description>AMRbook is an online reference guide to antimicrobial therapy. It provides doctors with a brief information on the most important practical aspects of treatment and prevention of infectious diseases. AMRbook&amp;rsquo;s database is replenished constantly with authoritative foreign and Russian treatment guidelines for antimicrobial use in infectious diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AMRcloud</title>
      <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/amr-cloud/</guid>
      <description>AMRcloud (AntiMicrobial Resistance Cloud) is a web platform for analysis of AMR survillance data that contains a set of tools to visualize the antimicrobial susceptibilities and genetic resistance determinants data in microbial isolates.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SNPT</title>
      <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/snpt/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/snpt/</guid>
      <description>Single nucleotide polymorphisms (SNPs) are the most abundant form of genetic variations in closely related microbial strains or isolates. In recent years, molecular methods based on analysis of informative sets of SNPs have gained increased application in bacterial genotyping. The SNPT web platform and databases are designed to assist in analysis of SNP typing data of the most common bacterial pathogens.
To speed up identification of genomes matching the defined SNP profiles, SNPT also extracts and stores in a local database the sequences of MLST loci from WGSs available in GenBank.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CityMap</title>
      <link>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/city-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://iacmac-web-tools.github.io/amrhub/en/services/city-map/</guid>
      <description>CityMap is a simple and convenient web-tool for data geo-visualization. The resource allows to pin markers and piecharts on the map of the Russian Federation (finding cities&amp;rsquo; coordinates automatically), and also to draw a regional heatmap.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>